<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<elements>
	<element name="Caliburn" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_CALIBURN">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;An ornate engraved sword emanating a calming and dim light around the blade. The pummel and guard, although a simplistic build, have finely made patterns that seem of a highly skilled artisan like no other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Pact Of Light&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On attuning to this weapon, the sword itself seems to judge you. The wielder must succeed a Strength save (DC 15). On a success the sword becomes attuned, however on a failure the target takes 1d8 Radiant damage and 1d8 Lightning damaged and cannot attempt Pact Of Light again until after a long rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a pact is made, this longsword grants +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it and gains the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Holy Touch:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On landing a melee attack with this weapon, it deals an additional 1d4 Radiant damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Static Charged&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On landing a melee attack with this weapon, it deals an additional 1d4 Lightning damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disintegrating Lifesteal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On landing a critical melee attack with this weapon, the wielder may choose to call down wrath from the heavens. The attack deals 4d6 Lightning damage and heals the wielder for 2d8 Hit Points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When this ability is used, the attuned cannot use &lt;strong&gt;Staic Charged&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Disintegrating Strike&lt;/strong&gt; until next dawn.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Sword</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">1</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_GROUP_SWORDS, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_SLASHING</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Gravewalker" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_GRAVEWALKER">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;A cold blade of steel and iron, with frozen shards of ice emanating from the blade and pummel giving an unnatural green/teal glow. The blade holds the spirit of the previous warrior who wielded it, waiting to deem whoever may be worthy to take up its frozen edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Haunting Pact&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On attuning to this weapon, the spirit within judges if its new wielder is worthy. The wielder must succeed a Charisma save (DC 15). On a success the sword becomes attuned, however on a failure the target takes 1d8 Cold damage and 1d8 Necrotic damage and cannot attempt Haunting Pact again until after a long rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a pact is made, this longsword grants +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it and gains the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frozen Touch:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On landing a melee attack with this weapon, it deals an additional 1d4 Cold damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dormant Spectre:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While its spirit is inside the sword, the blade deals and additonal 1d4 Necrotic damage on melee hits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenant Warrior:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an action, the wielder of this blade may call upon the spirit inside to fight along side them for up to one hour, and can use a bonus action to recall the spirit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spirit leaves the sword with a copy of the sword in hand. The spirit's turn is the same as the attuned's initiative and has a Hit Point total of 40 and an AC of 16. The spirit has a move speed up to 20ft and can make a single attack per turn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the spirit is summoned, &lt;strong&gt;Dormant Spectre&lt;/strong&gt; and&lt;strong&gt; Revenant Warrior&lt;/strong&gt; can no longer be used.
&lt;p&gt;If the spirit's hit points are reduced to 0 before returning to the sword, the spirit disappears. The attund then cannot use &lt;strong&gt;Dormant Spectre&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Revenant Warrior&lt;/strong&gt; until next dawn. If the spirit is recalled, you only must do a short rest before you can reuse the abilities.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Sword</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">1</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_GROUP_SWORDS, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_SLASHING</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Archdemon's Razor" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_ARCHDEMONS_RAZOR">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;A black blade made of a mysterious metal. A green eye petrudes from the center of the guard, blinking on its own accord. The eye is as mesmerizing as it is frightening, scaring most people away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Demon Pact&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On attuning to this weapon, the eye in the center of the blade pierces deep into your soul. The wielder must succeed an Intelligence save (DC 15). On a success the sword becomes attuned, however on a failure the target takes 1d8 Fire damage and 1d8 Psychic damage and cannot attempt Demon Pact again until after a long rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a pact is made, this longsword grants +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it and gains the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hellfire's Burn:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; On landing a melee attack with this weapon, it deals an additional 1d4 Fire damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dominant Gaze:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the eye is closed, the blade deals and additonal 1d4 Psychic damage on melee hits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demonic Presence:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a bonus action, the user of this blade may either open or close the eye of the blade. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the eye of the blade is open, it sends a constant violent aura to the wielders enemies. All targets within 100ft. must make a Wisdom saving throw (DC 16) or become frightened. While frightened by the sword, a creature must take the Dash action and move away from you at its max movement speed on each of its turns, unless there is nowhere to move. A creature under this effect can make a Wisdom saving throw at the begining of each of its turns. On a successful save, the spell ends for that creature. If the eye is closed, the spell ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the eye is closed while at least one creature is still under &lt;strong&gt;Demonic Presence&lt;/strong&gt; then the attuned can not use &lt;strong&gt;Dominant Gaze&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Demonic Presence&lt;/strong&gt; until next dawn. If at least two creatures manage to break free from the sword's gaze, the abiliteis cannot be used until next dawn as well.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Sword</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">1</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_GROUP_SWORDS, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_SLASHING</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Rift Breaker" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_RIFT_BREAKER">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;An elegant spear with a light purple shaft with strange glyphs inscribed on it. The blade seems to be a strange dark purple gem sharpened to a fine point. There is a very faint purple light emanating from the weapon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This magic weapon grants a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dimensional Door&lt;/strong&gt; (1/Day)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You Teleport yourself from your current location to any other spot you can see. You can also bring one willing creature of your size or smaller. The creature must be within 5 feet of you when you cast this spell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would arrive in a place already occupied by an object or a creature, you and any creature traveling with you each take 4d6 force damage, and the spell fails to Teleport you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rift Strike&lt;/strong&gt; (4/Day)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an action, you can momentarily pierce the veil between dimensions, creating two connecting rifts in the air just big enough for the spear to pass through. You may make a melee attack against a creature you see within 60ft. from any direction. You may also throw the spear in this way, changing the trajectory of the spear to whatever direction the connecting rift faces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If thrown this way, the weapon will automatically return to your hand by two connecting rifts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Escape Rift&lt;/strong&gt; (1/Day)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an action, you can drive the butt-end of the spear into the ground, instantly creating a 10ft diameter circle of teleportation. Lasting 1 round, all who enter the circle are teleported to the same random location.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Spear</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">2</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_CATEGORY_SIMPLE_MELEE, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_PIERCING, ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_PROPERTY_THROWN, ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_PROPERTY_VERSATILE, ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_GROUP_SPEARS</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Widow's Whisper" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_WIDOWS_WHISPER">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;A beautiful rifle made of black wood and blue steel. A silver spider's web inlay wraps around the firearm, extending towards the end of the barrel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This magic weapon grants a +3 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This firearm produces no flash or noise when it is fired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weapon attacks score a critical hit on a roll of 19 or 20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On a Critical Hit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You become invisible for 1 minute, or until your next attack.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Rifle</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">3</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_CATEGORY_FIREARM, ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_CATEGORY_MARTIAL_RANGED, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_PIERCING, ID_WOTC_DMG_WEAPON_PROPERTY_FIREARM_AMMUNITION, ID_WOTC_DMG_WEAPON_PROPERTY_FIREARM_RELOAD_5_SHOTS, ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_PROPERTY_TWOHANDED</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Caladbolg" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_CALADBOLG">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;A greatsword of exquisite make, with a rainbow blade and gilded gold for the handle, wrapped in red cloth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This magic weapon grants a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once per day as an action, you can use this weapon to make an attack that shoots bright multicolored lightning in a 100 foot line. Any creatures caught in the attack must make a DC 15 Dexterity saving throw. On a failure, the creature take 8d6 lightning damage, or half as much on a success.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Sword</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">1</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_GROUP_SWORDS, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_SLASHING</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
	<element name="Flaiamat" type="Magic Item" source="Voltorian's Dream Journal" id="ID_VDJ_MAGIC_ITEM_FLAIAMAT">
		<description>
			<html>&lt;p&gt;This flail is alive, and embodies the wrath of the dragon that was used to make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This magic weapon grants a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The flail has 5 charges and regains 1d4+1 charges daily at dawn. Each property consumers 1 charge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dragon's Breath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an action, you use one of the three head's breath weapon. The red or green head affect a 45-foot cone, and the blue head a 90-foot lone line that is 5 feet wide. Each creature must make a DC 15 Dexterity saving throw, taking 4d8 fire, lightning, or poison damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiamat's Bane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an action, you cast the &lt;strong&gt;Bane&lt;/strong&gt; spell (save DC 15), which affects any number creatures of your choice within range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dragon's Presence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each creature of your choice that is withing 120 feet and aware of this weapon must succedd on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or become frightened for 1 minute. A creature can repeat the saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on itself on a success. If a creature's saving throw is successful or the effect ends on it, the creature is immune to the dragon's presence for the next 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</html>
		</description>
		<setters>
			<set name="Keywords">Flail</set>
			<set name="Category">Magic Weapons</set>
			<set name="Type">Weapon</set>
			<set name="Attunement">True</set>
			<set name="Rarity">Very Rare</set>
			<set name="Enhancement">2</set>
			<set name="Weapon">ID_INTERNAL_WEAPON_CATEGORY_MARTIAL_MELEE, ID_INTERNAL_DAMAGE_TYPE_BLUDGEONING</set>
		</setters>
	</element>
</elements>